Robbers car owners of back if you do not have this
C then there will be no claim,
you will not be able to make any independent claim at all if you do
not have guide tuition yes yes what is C, from
where can it be made and
what is important then chair and what is
that lettuce under control, its meaning is the
most important what is K,
it is one normally you must have seen it many times anywhere,
go to any local garage,
go to Pipri service centers you get this,
how did you know in the system so that you can get it
in the green card, within the recent days
digitization frustration, now at this time a
political crisis has created a complete system
which is yes now we will tell you how
this entire PYSI is visualized,
engine chassis number, send photo on WhatsApp,
this is the photo type, there are properties in it
and there is an increase in waste,
its scream Gaurav Inspire had
introduced so much importance, I
explain that sensitive person has been
told that the pollution that happens is 14%
voucher  It comes through, yes, two wheeler is
40% more than four wheeler, how does that happen, so to
manage all this, to attend to all this, to be
able to control the properties page, so for this it is as important as
I have
tweeted that even now the document, so to
mash it you will always have to
check the love, to control pollution, by
subscribing to our channel
and if the subscription is less, please subscribe, I will be on this, I
made a very good video explaining its importance, its changes, its importance,
from school to
graduation, you should watch this video, you will get to know
that on the basis of this,
such truth is that on which someone walks, now let me
tell you that if you have any claim
or any car accident happens,
accuracy with RC insurance invoice, very married woman,
then please you because if you have
not increased the asking or please check
about yourself whether it is thirsty or not, go
to the ad service center, said that
go to democracy and please get your
thirsty right now  Hrithik, this is a very valid
document for cleaning and effect. Please make this
video known to as many people as possible.
Your friends and
relatives may not know. It is
important for you to know this video channel about what is going on
in the automobile industry. And if
you liked this video, please comment and
like it. Your likes will help us in getting recognition on
our account. On
one hand, there are many videos on the
automobile industry, from finance, whatever will be there,
we used to tell you immediately about
Silver Star and Ritz from its texture.